cheezhead.com 2016-12-02

# Privacy Statement - Recruiting.com

Recruiting.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to the privacy of our visitors and users. We give our best effort to ensure that the information that you submit to us remains private, and that information is utilized only for the purposes described herein. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for Recruiting.com.

## Personal Information & Non-Personal Information

You provide personal information to use when you communicate with our team by email, form, or online chat. We may also gather information about how you use and access our website and services, including your IP address, browser and other system information. We may use the information that you provide to us to improve your online experience, to provide client service and support, to send you information that we think may be useful to you, and for aggregate information about our site visitors.

## Sharing of Information to Third Parties

We do not sell personal information to third parties. In the event of a sale, merger, consolidation, or acquisition, any acquirer will be subject to our obligations under this Privacy Policy.

## Links

The Recruiting.com web site contains links to other sites through our advertisers and our resources for job seekers and employers. Recruiting.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites and web pages that are not part of the Jobing.com site.

## Cookies

Our site uses “cookies” to keep track of your site visit and to ensure that your experience is interactive. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and your searches in order to give you a unique experience on Recruiting.com properties. In addition to various other purposes, we also utilize cookies to save your password so you don’t have to re-enter it each time you visit our site. Please note that Recruiting.com websites may not work properly for you if you have cookies disabled. Cookies do not pose any security risk to your computer.

## Newsletter

Recruiting.com offers an electronic e-mail newsletter for employers who utilize the Recruiting.com website. We ask for the user’s e-mail address to distribute the newsletter, and you may choose not to receive the e-mail newsletter on the Recruiting.com website.

## Feedback

Please [send feedback](mailto:marketing@recruiting.com) to the webmaster. We appreciate the opportunity to hear from you, and we review all of your comments. All feedback that is submitted to us becomes the property of Recruiting.com, and we may utilize it for other purposes, including, but not limited to, marketing.

## Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.

## Choice/Opt-Out

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor.

## Statement Changes

Any changes to our privacy statement will be posted on this page of our web site.
